这个显然没用
死冰箱
乔伊，你好吗？
很好，室友
我们现在的确是室友
没错，经你一提
我们的冰箱坏了，得买台新的
我打听过，你得出4百
感激不尽
我才不跟你分
我只住到我们那边整理好
瑞秋，这台冰箱是我出生之后
我父母买的
我用都没问题
你一来它就坏了
这意味着什么？
冰箱无法和人一样长寿
好，你也知道自动提款机
一次只能提3百
剩下的1百我就收支票
你在开玩笑吧？
那当然，我不收支票
幸好你很帅
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=-
河马压缩制作
本集播出：“罗斯的烦恼”
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
你们有认识的帅哥吗？
当然有
就是我的好朋友乔伊
我忘了…谢谢你
周末有大型慈善晚会
监制：塔德史帝文斯
罗夫罗兰买了一桌，我也得去
为什么兑款？
不晓得
不是某种树就是某种病…
监制：安德鲁瑞屈
罗夫很会碎碎念
监制：泰德柯恩
罗夫都趁你不专心时碎碎念吗
对呀，好奇怪
编剧吉吉麦克里利、派瑞瑞恩
总之我得找个男伴
你想找什么样的人？
自己有晚礼服或租得起晚礼服
所以身家起码要有50元
导演：班威斯
只差一点
大家好
这是伊丽莎白
我就是那个学生
真可爱…才怪
也许我不该多嘴
但你们在一起不是不能被看到
我们没有在一起
没有，我们只是两个
在咖啡馆巧遇的人
真奸诈
我很想多认识你们
但是我得走了
改天见
好
罗斯再见
再见
老师，我不是故意撞到你的
没关系
她为什么要走？
刚放学功课一大堆？
对，她明天要交
分子流行病学报告
帮我祝她好运
还有吗？别客气
她什么时候生日？
我不知道，怎么了？
我好久没吃儿童生日餐了
我喜欢伊丽莎白
谢谢
我真的很喜欢她
叫她今年早点送女童军饼干来
我要薄荷巧克力饼和巧克力派
你们别闹他了
说真的，你们交往得怎样？
非常好
她才20岁，还不想太认真
最适合现在的我
太好了，她真的好像很不错
谢谢，我知道你们喜欢臭我
但我真的很希望你们能喜欢她
只要知道你们…
我想到一个很棒的
好，她是才12岁吗？
钱德，你觉得我们的沟通够吗
够，有水果卷吗？
我刚想到一个人
很适合当瑞秋的男伴
有意思，我们也找到人了
那好，她可以在我的人
和你们的怪胎之中选一个
为什么我们的人是怪胎？
你们的品味就是那样
瑞秋才不会选你的蠢人
是吗？
没错
我这个是律师，还当义工
而且他有这个东西
脸屁股？
下巴窝啦
我们这个是钱德的同事
人好聪明又会打扮
你们看过他的身体吗？
没有，他是一颗飘来飘去的头
我这个身材很赞
他是我的客人
有一次他在按摩台上
就被我看光光了
你不能偷看
警察又不会抓
你会偷看？我给你按摩过
没错
好，你那个或许身材很好
但我们这个很风趣
钱德式的风趣？
我们这个舞功高强
我这个饱读诗书
我们这个发质很好
我这个牙齿漂亮
我们这个香得不得了
你真这么哈他？
你的脸色不太好
冰箱坏了，我得把东西都吃掉
冷盘、冰淇淋、莱姆…
咖啡色罐子里是什么？
那个还在？
现在不在了
总之你要怎么付钱给我？
你要提供某种服务吗？
不是，是我要买冰箱
我们要买冰箱
我们？我已经不住这里了
那又怎样？
假设我们是离婚夫妻
我取得孩子的监护权
结果孩子死了
我总得买个新孩子
好
给我4百元
幸好你很帅
盖勒教授
一名我不认识的学生
能不能跟您谈一下？
当然可以，是哪方面的事？
在你的研究室亲热
好，我们进去再说
怎么了？
门把
抱歉
我真的有事要讲
好，什么事？
春假的事
春假的事？
对，学校没课
很多人要去旅行…
盖勒教授
是，菲森死盯个乐教授…
我马上就好
那我就买一盒薄荷巧克力饼
你们不懂
伊丽莎白想找我跟她去旅行
这样叫慢慢来吗？
我还没准备好，我该怎么说？
实话实说，说你还没准备好
可以试试
要是她不高兴呢？
你就拿芭比娃娃逗她
或者你也可以…
你干什么？
我干什么？你弄坏我的冰箱
什么？你怎么知道它坏了？
它怎么坏的我会不知道吗？
你等一下
看吧，坏了
请赔4百
乔伊，我看见你推他了
是你推的
乔伊，我没把它弄坏
它已经坏一阵子了
我不是提过我们的冰箱的事？
我还没拿到你该出的钱
不要给他钱
你少插嘴，你撞坏我的冰箱
盖勒教授，你找我？
是的，请进
门把？
对，你有点玩上瘾了
我想继续上次春假的话题
好
听我说，我…
我跟你在一起很开心
我不想进展得太快
或是给我们太多压力
所以很抱歉
我们还不能一起旅行，太快了
罗斯，你误会我的意思了
我只是想告诉你
我要去佛罗里达2星期
不，是你误会我的意思了
我的意思是…
你好可爱
这个，我们来讨论这个
你跟伊丽莎白谈得怎样？
没事，只是一场误会
她没有要找我去
她只是要告诉我她要去放春假
等等，她是去放春假
还是去春游？
有什么差别？
春假是跟爷爷奶奶共享天伦
春游是跟兄弟会的人上床
并非每个人的春游都那样
你做了什么？
我跟我爸去埃及
我可以想像
“爸，是人面狮身像”
伊丽莎白那么正经
不会去“春游”
好吗？她修了我的课
还跟教授上床
我去打给她
各位，这是赛巴斯钦
我们刚刚在报摊认识
我们都买了“原野与河流”
我有在看啊
你要咖啡吗？
要，谢谢
瑞秋，你这是什么意思？
什么？
你叫我们帮你找人
却自己带了个人来
你们帮我找到人了？
对，我们在钱德的公司
相中一个可爱风趣的人
我也找了一个不是怪胎的人
你们知道吗？真是谢谢你们
不过我带赛巴斯钦去就好了
你确定？我们这个很香喔
别再提那个了好吗？
你的咖啡
赛巴斯钦，你有在当义工吗？
没有，怎么了？
没事，我只是认识一个
关心别人的单身汉
你风趣吗？
什么？
你们在干什么？
你风趣吗？讲个笑话来听
我只是想和瑞秋喝杯咖啡
很多人都想
说实话我该走了
有空打电话给我
你没给我电话号码
好，那就改天见
原来他蛮风趣的
你们真是太扯了
他人很好，却被你们赶走了
赛巴斯钦耶？
那是猫的名字吗？
你知道我发现什么？
他很容易被吓到
你想带这种人参加舞会吗？
“赛巴斯钦，要不要跳舞？”
“好，我得走了”
别再说了
瑞秋，对不起，我们太过份了
这样吧，让我们补偿你
我们有两个好男人让你挑
对啊，你有什么损失？
搞不好会认识让你心动的人
如果你选我这边的话
好吧
你愿意见我们找的人？
我愿意
你要选谁都行，由你自己决定
我们这个很完美
或者你也可以选
菲比自己看不上眼的人
菲比，你在这里
你弄坏我的冰箱，欠我4百
好吧
真的？
技术上来说你欠我6百
你最近十次试镜我都有祝祷
那就扯平了？
好吧
回来了，伊丽莎白怎么说？
她真的是要去德通纳春游
也就是有湿T恤美女选拔赛
男生朝女生身上扔水球
在陌生人身边醒来
她会玩得很爽
她要住可乐娜饭店吗？
你熟那里的饭店？
当然，我参加过81年春游
81年你才13岁
那又怎样？我开车去卖T恤
玩得好开心
你们知道谁最会疯？
酒醉的大学女生
好，她不准去
罗斯，你不能叫她不要去
你们才交往没多久
那我该怎么办？
不怎么办，你只能接受
要是她跑去跟一堆人上床呢？
那这次你就别娶她
对不起，这是很严肃的事
你知道吗？你喜欢她
她也喜欢你，不会有事的
你说得对，我反应过度了
她要住在滨海饭店
有大游泳池，每顿都吃大餐…
她既然这么有钱
一定能赔偿她弄坏的冰箱
你能去旅行真是好事
就是啊，我这学期那么用功
很需要疯狂一下，缓解压力
当然
我不知道你的计划底定了没
还有一个办法可以缓解压力
什么办法？
你喜欢做手工艺吗？
罗斯，你还好吗？
我当然很好
我只是在表示支持
支持你和这次旅行
还有这是什么？
那是泳衣
你要穿它去见人？
这样叫支持吗？
这样是吗？
太好了
很高兴你答应见我们找的人
你一定会很喜欢他
你要什么时候见他？
不晓得
我知道我明天不用加班
明天不错…
不过现在能做的事
为什么要拖到明天？
艾达，过来
艾达，这位是瑞秋
你好吗？
有点措手不及，不过我很好
艾达，坐…你坐过去
这就对了
好，我们知道了
你来干什么？
这位是派屈克
你来晚了
她跟我们那个在一起了
天哪，我是来晚了
他们正坐在沙发上聊天
瑞秋
怎样？
这是派屈克
他就是我说的那个人
相信我，这套西装
太委屈底下的身材了
好，但是菲比
怎样？
我现在有点事
好，没关系，你坐
你不能这样
我走好了
坐下，我们占上风
也许我才应该走
不要，坐下
瑞秋，你还没摸过艾达的头发
超柔顺的，你摸摸看
不必了
瑞秋，派屈克很有钱
拿钱给她
这个免费按摩的代价太高了
没错，派屈克，再见
艾达合作多了，而且很会跳舞
你跳舞给瑞秋看
不，拜托不要
你们是怎么搞的？
没错，大家来说清楚
我…
只有我觉得尴尬吗？
我也有点尴尬
该尴尬的是你们
这实在是太扯了
很谢谢你们
但我不需要你们帮我找人
那你为什么叫我们…
我还没说完
你们还把我真正喜欢的人赶走
我没有冒犯的意思，真的
恭喜你有那么多现金
还有你…你的头发真的很柔顺
但我宁可自己参加晚会
也不要再受这种气，再见
你有用什么特别的润发乳吗？
有，木瓜粹取液
谢谢
好好去玩吧
我会的
你有带那套泳衣吗？
有
我刚才把它藏起来
实在蛮好笑的
总之…
我不是担心那套泳装太曝露
这一点我不在意
我是关心你的健康，怕你晒到
放心，我带了一大堆防晒油
防晒系数30
如果真的有30就好了
有时候是30，有时候只有4
我发誓有很多都只是牛奶
罗斯，你放心
我不是要去跟一堆男生鬼混
我很喜欢你
我喜欢我们的关系
真的？
对，我只是跟朋友们去玩一玩
好吧
他们来了
伊丽莎白
打电话给我
瑞秋，抱歉把那些人硬塞给你
没关系，结果我玩得很开心
晚会很成功
兑到很多款，引起很多重视
它是为什么兑款？
我很想说是一种疾病
罗斯留了奇怪的留言
叫我们看MTV台
看，是伊丽莎白
盖勒教授
重温旧梦
是啊
Mandarin-R3
Well,that thing's clearly in the way.
All right.
Damn fridge!
-Hi,Joey. How you doing?
-Great...
roomie.
-I guess we are roommates.
-I know.Now that you bring it up,
our fridge is broken.We need a new one.
I checked and your half is $400. Thanks a lot.
I'm not paying for that.I'm just here while they fix my place.
Look,Rach,my parents bought this fridge just after I was born. Okay?
I have never had a problem with it. Then you show up and it breaks!
What does that tell you?
That refrigerators don't live as long as people?
You know the ATM only lets you take out 300,so...
I'll take a check for the rest.
You're joking,right?
Of course I'm joking. I don't take checks.
Thank God,you're pretty.
The One With Joey's Fridge
Hi! Do you guys know any cute guys?
Of course. My good friend Joey over here.
I'm sorry. Thank you,Chandler.
There's a charity ball and Ralph Lauren has a table...
so I have to go.
-What charity?
-I don't know.
Something,either trees or disease...
Ralph mumbles a lot.
-He mumbles when you're not attentive?
-Yeah. It's weird.
But I need to find a date.
What kind of date?
Someone that has his own tux or the ability to rent a tux.
So he has to be a male who has at least $50.
So close.
-Hey,everybody!
-Hi,there.
-This is Elizabeth.
-Hi,Elizabeth.
I'm the student.
Isn't she cute? Nope.
Weren't you guys supposed to...not be seen together?
We aren't.
We just happen to have run into each other here.
Oh,sly!
I wanted to meet you guys,but I have to run.
-See you later?
-Okay.
-Bye,Ross.
-Bye. See you.
-Didn't mean to run into you,sir.
-That's quite all right,ma'am.
Why is she leaving? Is it a school night and she has homework?
Yes. Her molecular epidemiology paper is due tomorrow.
Tell her good luck with that.
Anyone else? Bring them on.
-When's her birthday?
-I don't know. Why?
It's just been so long since I've been to Chuck E. Cheese.
-I like Elizabeth.
-Well,thanks.
I like her so much,tell her I want my cookies early this year.
A box of Thin Mints and some Tagalongs.
Give him a break. Ross,how's it going with her?
It's been great.
She's 20,so she's not too serious,which is perfect for me now.
That's great. Seriously,she seems nice.
I know you guys like to give me a hard time...but it means a lot to me.
-Just knowing..
-Okay,I got a good one.
What is she,like,12?
Chandler,do we talk about our relationship enough?
Yeah. Do we have any Fruit Roll-Ups?
I thought of the perfect guy for Rachel to take to her thing.
That's so funny. We found someone too.
Good. She'll have a choice between my guy and your weirdo.
-Why would our guy be a weirdo?
-Because that's just your taste.
See,Rachel's not gonna pick your stupid guy.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
My guy is a lawyer,who does volunteer work.
And he has one of these.
A face ass?
A chin dimple.
Well,you know,our guy works with Chandler.He's really nice and smart,and he's a great dresser.
-Have you seen your guy's body?
-No. Our guy's just a floating head.
Well,my guy is spectacular. He's a massage client.
And one time,when he was on the table,I looked at it. And I mean all of it.
-You're not supposed to look.
-Like there are police for that.
You look? You massaged me.I know.
Fine. Your guy may have a great body,but our guy is really funny.
Chandler funny?
-Our guy's a great dancer.
-My guy's well-read.
-Our guy has great hair.
-My guy has great teeth.
Our guy smells incredible.
Do you want our guy to be your guy?
Well,you don't look good,Joe.
The fridge broke,so I had to eat everything.
Cold cuts,ice cream,limes.
What was in that brown jar?
-That's still in there?
-Not anymore.
So anyway,how do you want to pay me?
Is this a service you're providing me?
No,for my new fridge. For our new fridge.
Our new fridge?I don't live here anymore.
-So what?Look,okay,suppose we were a divorced couple
And I got custody of the kid. Right?
Now suppose the kid dies and I gotta buy a new kid.
Okay.
Give me $400!
Thank God,you're pretty.
Professor Geller?
Oh,a student I don't know.
I was wondering if I could talk to you for a moment?
Yes,of course. What would this be regarding?
Making out in your office.
Of course. Why don't we go inside.
-What?
-Doorknob.
Sorry.
I actually do need to talk to you.What about?
-Spring vacation?
Yeah,we have time off,and a lot of people are going on trips..
-Professor Geller.
-Yes,Professor Friesenstinlender.
I'll be with you in one moment.
So I will take one box of the Thin Mints.
You don't understand. Elizabeth was about to ask me to go on a trip with her.
Is that taking it slow?
-I'm not ready for this.What do I tell her?
-Tell her the truth,tell her you're not ready.
I could do that.
-What if she gets upset?
-Then you distract her with a Barbie doll.
Or you could just,you know,you...
What the hell are you doing?
What the hell am I doing? You just broke my fridge!
What? How do..?How do you know it's even broken?
You think I don't know what breaks my fridge?
Excuse me!
Well,what do you know?Broken!
That'll be $400.
Joey,I saw you push him.
You pushed him.
Joey,I did not break this. Okay? That has been broken for a while.
Remember I told you about our fridge?
I still haven't gotten the check for your half yet.
Do not give him any money!I'm not talking to you! You broke my fridge!
-You wanted to see me,Professor Geller?
-Yes. Please come in.
-Doorknob?
-Yeah. It kind of grows on you.
I wanted to finish talking to you about spring vacation.Good.
Look,I...
Look,I'm having a great time with you.
And I just don't want us to move too fast or put too much pressure on us.
So I'm sorry,I just don't think we should go away together yet.It's too soon.
Ross,I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
I just wanted to tell you that I'm going to Florida for a couple weeks.
No.I think you misunderstood what I was saying.
What I meant was..You are so adorable.
That. Let's talk about that.
-Hi.
-Hi.How did it go with Elizabeth?
Fine. Just a misunderstanding.
She didn't want me to go with her.She just wanted to let me know she's going to Florida for a spring vacation.
Wait a minute. Is she going for spring vacation or spring break? Wahoo!
What's the difference?
Spring vacation,you're doing nice things with your grandparents.
Spring break,you're doing frat guys.
You know what? Not all spring breaks are like that.
-What did you do on yours?
-I went to Egypt with my dad.
I can see it now. "Look,Dad,it's the Sphinx,wahoo!"
I think Elizabeth is a little more serious than: "Spring break,wahoo!"
Come on,she's taking my class.
-And slept with the professor.
-I'm gonna call her.
You guys,I want you to meet Sebastian.
We met at the newsstand. We both grabbed for the last Field and Stream.
What? I read that.
-Can I get you a cup of coffee?
-Yes. Thank you.
-Rachel,what the hell is this?
-What?You ask us to find a guy,
and you come traipsing in here with a guy of your own?
You found me a guy?
Yes. We found you a really cute,funny guy from Chandler's work.
Yeah,and I found you one too,who is not a weirdo.
You know what though,guys,I really appreciate that...but I'm gonna take Sebastian
Are you sure? Our guy smells incredible.
Would you stop it with that already?
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
So,Sebastian,do you do any volunteer work?
-Not really. Why?
-No reason.I know a single guy who does care about other people.
Are you funny?
-Excuse me?
-What are you guys doing?
Are you funny? Tell us a joke!
I just wanted to have coffee with Rachel.
Well,so do a lot of people.
-Actually,I gotta get going.
-But you..
-Give me a call sometime.
-You didn't give me your phone number.
Okay,see you later.
Turns out he is kind of funny.
I cannot believe you guys!He was really nice,and he just left because of you!
Yeah,but "Sebastian"? What is that,a cat's name?
You know what I noticed,Rachel? He scares easy.
Is that the kind of guy you wanna take to a ball?
"Hey,Sebastian,would you like to dance?"
"Okay. I gotta go."
Stop it.
Rachel,we're very sorry.That is a very insensitive thing to do.
Let us make it up to you. We have two really great guys for you.
Yeah,what have you got to lose?You might even end up with someone really special.
If you pick my guy.
-All right.
-So you will meet our guys?Yes
It doesn't matter which one you choose. It's up to you.
Our guy is perfect.
Or you could go out with the guy Phoebe deemed not good enough for herself.
There you are! You broke my fridge.You owe me $400.
-Okay,sure.
-Really?
Technically,you owe me $600 for sending out happy thoughts...on your last 10 auditions.
Call it even?
Okay.
There you are.What did Elizabeth say?
Turns out she is going to Daytona for "spring break,wahoo."
That means wet T-shirt contests,guys doing shots off of girls' bodies...
waking up with strangers.
She is gonna have a great time!
Is she staying at the Hotel Corona?
-You know the hotels?
-I was there! Spring Break '81,wahoo!
In 1981,you were 13.
So? I drove down,sold T-shirts. Had a blast.
You know who knows how to party? Drunk college chicks.
Okay,she can't go.
You can't tell her not to go. You just started dating.
-What am I supposed to do?
-You just have to be cool with it.
What if she goes down there and sleeps with a bunch of guys?
Well,maybe you don't marry this one.
I'm sorry,this is very serious.
And you know what,Ross?You like her,she likes you,everything's gonna be fine.
You're right. I'm probably overreacting.
It's just she's staying at this party hotel on the beach...with a huge pool and free drinks with every meal.
If she's got enough money for that,she can certainly pat for the fridge she broke.
I'm so glad you're going on this trip.I've been working so hard this semester.
I really need to go crazy,blow off some steam.Sure.
Look,I don't know if your plans are finalized yet,but...
I know a great way to blow off steam.
-What?
-Are you into crafts at all?
Ross,are you okay?
Yeah. Of course I'm okay.I'm just being supportive.
Supportive of you and this whole trip...and what's this?
It's a bathing suit?To wear in front of people?
Is that supportive?Is this?
Okay,good.
-Hey.
-Hi.We're so glad you decided to meet our guy. You'll like him so much.
-When do you want to meet him?
-I don't know.I don't work late tomorrow night.
-Tomorrow night is good.
But why put off something till tomorrow that you could do it right now?
-Eldad,come here!
-What?
-This is Rachel.
-How are you?
A little blindsided but good.
Eldad,sit down. Move over now.
There you go. There you are.
Okay,we can take a hint!
What? What are you doing here?This is Patrick.
-Hi.
-Hi.You're too late because she's already with our guy.
You're right,I am too late. They're sitting on the couch and talking.
Rachel?
This is Patrick.
-Hi.
-Hi.This is the guy I was telling you about.
This suit does not do justice to what's underneath it.
Okay.But,Phoebe,
I'm just sort of in the middle of something.
Okay. That's okay. Have a seat.
-You can't do that!
-I should go.Sit down,we're winning.
Maybe I should go.No. Have a seat!
Rachel,you haven't touched Eldad's hair.
-He has the softest hair. Touch it.
-I'm good.
Rachel,Patrick is really rich. Give her some money.
This isn't really worth the free massage.
-That's right. Bye-bye.
-No.
Eldad is much more cooperative,and he can dance.
You dance for Rachel.
Don't dance for me. Please!
What is the matter with you?
Yeah,let's talk it out.
Am I the only one that this is embarrassing for?
I'm a little embarrassed.
I'll tell you who should be embarrassed. It's you guys.
I do not need you to get me a date.
-Why did she ask us to..?
-I am still talking!
Then you chase away the one guy I actually liked.
No offense to you guys. Really,congratulations on...all the cash.
And you really do have very soft hair.
But I'd much rather go to the ball by myself than go through any more of this.Goodbye.
Now,do you use some sort of special conditioner on that hair?
Papaya extract.Thank you.
So have a great time down there
-I will. -Yeah.
Did you pack that bathing suit?
-Yeah.
It was pretty funny when I hid it for a while.
Anyway.
I am worried about that suit.Not because it's revealing,which I'm fine with.
I'm concerned about your health.Sun exposure.
Don't worry,I have plenty of sun block
-It's SPF 30. -All right.
Well,if what's in the bottle is actually 30.
Sometimes you get 30,sometimes it's 4 and...more often than not,it's just milk.
Ross,it's gonna be okay.I'm not going down there to hook up with a bunch of guys.
I really like you.I like how things are going between us.
-Really?
-Yeah.I'm just going down there to relax and hang out with my friends.
Okay. Cool.
Here they are!
Call me!
Sorry for pushing those guys on you.
That's all right. I ended up having a really good time.
The charity was a big success,and they raised a lot of money and awareness.
So,what was it for anyway?
I wanna say a disease.
I just got this really weird message from Ross. He said to turn on MTV.
Oh,my God,look! That's Elizabeth!
Professor Geller.
To be 13 again....